Darryl Dixon

Newport News, Virginia http://PieceDigital.github.io http://github.com/PieceDigital PieceDigitalStudios@gmail.com

Summary

I'm a self-coached web developer with a passion for building websites and web apps with great user experience. My specialty is in improving web presence, company reputation, and greater user retention by developing engaging, functional, and beautiful web products.

Skills

- Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript/Node
- JavaScript Libraries and Frameworks: jQuery, ReactJS, AngularJS(basic), ExpressJS, Socket.io
- Tools: Photoshop, Git (and GitHub), Gulp Handlebars.js, Sass
- Others: Responsive Design, Mentoring

Experience

Guide Magazine Aug 2015 - Oct 2015

Web App Developer

- Created a fully featured JavaScript chat application, complete with admin panel: http://piecedigital.github.io/gcc-chat
- Designed the app to be touchscreen-friendly and responsive across desktop and mobile
- Constructed server code to be modular and efficient

MTM Landscaping

Mar 2015 - May 2015

Freelance Web Developer/Consultant

- Assisted in design decisions
- Constructed web code for optimal load times

Meraki Natural Hair

Oct 2014 - May 2015

Web Designer/Developer

- Designed the website to be aesthetically comfortable and pleasing, using wireframes and mockup as guides for implementation
- Constructed web code to be manageable and efficient

Education

Free Code Camp Oct 2014 - Apr 2015

• Completed this online curriculum in 6 months, where I learned full-stack web development

CodeCademy Oct 2014 - Apr 2015

• A general online course where I learned the essentials of web development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)